smarttradefx.com 2013-06-30

# SmartTradeFX - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

At SmartTradeFX, Inc. (STFX) protecting your privacy is important to us. Our Company is committed to safeguarding the personally identifiable financial information you provide us as part of the trading account process. We want you to understand what information we collect and how we use consumer information in order to provide our clients premier services and products. The following information outlines STFX's Privacy Policy and briefly describes how we treat non-public personal information.

**Information STFX Collects**

We may collect non-public personal information about you from the following sources: * Information provided by you on an application or other forms such as your name, address, date of birth social security number, occupation, assets, and income. * Information about your transactions with us or our affiliates. * Information we receive from non-affiliated service providers, including reporting agencies. When you apply for or maintain an account with STFX, we collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, or informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you, plus providing client services.

**Information STFX May Disclose**   
STFX does not disclose any non-public personal information about you to either our affiliates or non affiliates except as permitted by law. We limit access to staff members who conduct our business, service your account, and help you accomplish your financial objectives, such as providing you with a broad range of products and services. We may also disclose your non-public information as described above to persons or companies that perform services on our behalf. In addition, we may disclose personal information with non-affiliated companies and regulatory authorities as permitted or required by applicable law. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property.

**Sharing Information with Our Affiliates**   
We may share personal information described above with our affiliates for business purposes, such as servicing client accounts and informing consumers about new products and services as permitted by applicable law. Our affiliates are companies under common control with STFX or controlled in whole or in part by STFX including financial service companies, such as dealers, other brokers, futures commission merchants, and advisers.

**Verifying Your Personal Information**  
Keeping our client information up-to-date and accurate is important to us. You are allowed reasonable access to the information we have about you. Most of this information is contained in account statements that you receive from us and applications that you submit to obtain our products and services. We encourage you to review this information and notify us if you believe any information should be corrected or updated. Information related to a claim, criminal or civil proceedings may not be reviewed and updated.

**Security Procedures**   
We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your non-public personal information. Should your relationship with us end, we will maintain and only disclose non-public personal information that we have about you in accordance with this Privacy Notice.

Request for More Detailed Information This Notice is a summary of our Privacy Policy. If you would like a more detailed explanation regarding STFX's information practices, please send your request in writing to us at:

SmartTradeFX  
Suite 305, Griffith Corporate Centre, Beachmont, Kingstown, Saint Vincent and the Grenadines
